A date with me?
I'm surprised.
Where did that come from, Shin?
Is that a no?
We should still have a whole day
before DEM's assault.
That's true, but there's
no need to train for that, right?
This isn't for training!
With the final battle drawing near,
that's all the more reason
I want to invite you on a date.
Do the others know?
I haven't told them.
Why me?
You don't want to?
I haven't said that,
but if you wanted to go on a date with someone,
then you should have other options.
That won't do.
I want to go on a date with you, Reine.
I'll make some time.
Where should we go?
I see.
Reine is your best friend.
I'm sure you're shocked to hear
all of this so suddenly, but...
Thank you.
I'm sure it was hard for you, too.
Thank you for telling me.
Kotori...
Well then, let's come up with
a strategy without Reine noticing.
Yeah, let's do that.
To start, we'll have to think of
what to do for Reine's date by morning,
all while simultaneously
preparing our strategies against DEM.
That's true, also...
Deal with the other Spirits?
Yeah.
Reine was a reliable older sister
they all could trust.
When they learn that she betrayed them...
True.
Though we'll need them to get over that.
Origami Tobiichi
Cell Phone
Calling
Answer Cancel
Origami?
I heard what's going on.
Huh?
I've informed all the Spirits, too.
We'll help you compose your date plan.
H-Hold on a moment.
You heard?
How did you...?
Shido, your second button.
Huh?
Ah!
I understand what's going on!
I heard the details from Origami.
That was a surprise,
but there's no time to be depressed.
Now these are some hot developments
happening without my knowledge!
I kind of like this stuff!
Impressive, Reine Murasame!
You managed to deceive Kaguya Yamai!
Petition. Please let us help you, too.
All right.
Then assemble in the briefing room.
Go one at a time so Reine
doesn't catch on if you run into her.
Kotori, could you give me a bit of time?
Huh?
There's something I have to do.
I want to talk.
You're there, right, Kurumi?
You, huh?
My, my, this is unusual.
You're actually summoning me for once.
Are you the only one here right now?
Is the real Kurumi listening
into this conversation?
You ask quite the odd question.
None of the other clones
or the real me are here.
If you want to discuss something
you don't want the real me to hear,
then you're safe on that front.
I see.
I don't know if what I'm about to tell you
is safe to pass on to the real Kurumi.
So could you listen
and make that decision for me?
On February 20th, the real Kurumi
will die.
You speak like you've actually seen it happen.
Yeah, your guess is correct.
Who are you suggesting
managed to take me down?
Even if I'm about to face Ellen Mathers,
I won't go down that easily, you know.
It was Mio Takamiya.
The Spirit of Origin will kill Kurumi.
Mio suddenly appeared from within
Kurumi on the future battlefield.
I believe Mio is already inside of Kurumi.
So that's what happens.
I'm grateful.
You're right, this isn't information
to be handled carelessly.
So?
Do you think you can convey this
to Kurumi without Mio catching wind of it?
Most likely, yes.
Though, the real problem is
what to do about it afterwards.
Right.
I hope there's something
I can do to help, but...
Please don't make such a sad face.
I know this is a desperate situation,
but thanks to you I now have options.
Shido, was I able to fulfill
my duty in the future?
Yeah, in the coolest way possible.
Is that so?
R-Reine?! What are you doing?!
Working.
I figured I would take care of
tomorrow's work, too.
I finally finished up.
I see!
Good work, then!
And what are you up to at this hour, Tohka?
W-Well, um, uh...
If you want a late-night snack,
you should go to the cafeteria
or the break area.
Though go easy on the snacks,
given how late it is.
And don't forget to
brush your teeth before bed.
Y-Yes, I'll be careful.
I understand why you can't sleep,
but make sure to get rest.
We have to do everything we can
to protect Shin from DEM, after all.
Reine.
Hmm?
Reine... do you like Shido?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Just answer the question. Please.
Yeah, I like him.
I see. Yeah. Me, too!
No, I'm overthinking it.
Amamiya Station
Hello, Shido.
How's the bone conduction receiver working?
I can hear you clearly.
Though it is slightly different than usual.
Reine would catch on
if we used the usual transceiver.
We won't have to worry about
her noticing with this.
She should be arriving soon, so get ready.
All right.
Hey, did I keep you waiting?
R-Reine?!
It's finally starting.
Now, let our date begin.
Honestly, I still can't believe it.
Our Reine is Phantom?
I feel the same way.
But we have to accept the facts.
Still, it's not something
to be pessimistic about.
According to the boy, the friendship
she feels toward us is the real deal, too.
Exactly.
So in short, as long as Shido can make
Reine fall for him and seal her power,
then all of this will be resolved peacefully.
What's the matter, Shin?
Did I shock you that much?
Oh, no, um...
1) I'm sorry, I was captivated by you.
2) That's not your usual hairstyle, is it? It's lovely.
3) What'll it take to let me strip that outfit off of you?
Everyone, choices!
Yeah!
1, huh?
That's most reasonable.
Yes.
I think going silent
would only make her anxious.
But if he says that, she'll be happy.
Huh? Such consideration! Are you a goddess?
What does it say about me
that I chose the other
because I think we should wait and see for now.
Yes, I think Reine
will approve of this one, too!
Hmm. I don't think 2 is a bad choice either.
Well, whatever.
Indeed!
God dwells in the details.
It's important to notice
the minor changes, but...
Addendum. Depending on the person,
some might take it as suggesting
their usual hairstyle isn't that great.
I think we should play it safe
and wait and see.
So, what do you three think?
No, it's clearly 3 here!
Hearing such a surprising comeback
from such an innocent young boy
would really turn a lady on!
Right!
Reine is a mature woman, too,
so she'll appreciate wit like that.
Listen...
our future is riding on this,
so could you please take this seriously?
We know.
That's why we chose the line that
would make us the happiest to hear.
Shido, go with 1.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I've never seen you dressed
like this before, so well...
I was captivated.
Hmm?
I see.
Hmm, is that so?
Thank you.
Your outfit is wonderful, too.
Th-Thank you.
Now, where are we going today?
It looks like you brought a lot of luggage?
That's still a secret for now.
I want to surprise you.
Will you trust me and follow along?
Yes, of course.
Shall we go, then?
What's the matter?
This is technically a date, right?
Yes, it is. No technically about it.
Hmm, in that case...
Shall we go?
Yes.
Her affection rating...
is a strange wave pattern.
It looks like she holds enough affection
for us to be able to seal her at any moment,
but it's not triggering
the possibility to seal her.
It's like she holds deep affection for him,
but she's keeping herself at a distance.
Almost like she's affectionately
watching over him from the sidelines
while everyone else
gets to be on stage with him.
One could also say it's like a mother?
I see, that's oddly well put.
Either way, it doesn't change the fact
she'll be a difficult target.
This is...
Reine's affection is climbing!
Looks like your strategy
is working, Commander!
It wasn't solely my idea.
It's the result of all of us spirits
ironing out a plan until late last night.
A day trip to a hot springs inn on the weekend?
This really is an attractive choice.
Analyst Murasame is the one
who works the most in Fraxinus, too.
She also works as a teacher
at Raizen High on top of that.
She's also been working to revive
Shinji Takamiya for decades as well.
Even if she is a Spirit, it's only
natural that's she built up fatigue.
Reine always does have bags under her eyes.
I thought she must be struggling with her work.
I'm sure she doesn't get
much sleep every night.
Her mind and body should both
be completely exhausted.
So what Reine needs is relaxation!
She can use the various relaxation services
to relieve her pent up weariness and fatigue!
Oh!
1) Take it easy and stretch out in the large bath
2) Relax in the private outdoor bath
3) Get a refreshing massage
Everyone, choices!
Yeah!
Hmm, yeah, 2.
Yes, though I don't feel good about Reine
and Shido taking a bath alone together.
Yes.
I think they both need to
be able to talk a lot.
It's okay. I'm calm. I'm calm. I'm calm.
Huh? Why did you need to say that thrice?
Besides, I've been alone
in the bath with Shido, too.
I shouldn't be losing my calm
over something like this.
Hold on!
That was when you were lying in wait
to ambush him, wasn't it?!
You can't leave us Yamai sisters out
when it comes to bathing.
Affirmative.
Sandwiching Shido between me
and Kaguya was a nice memory.
They should be spending
some time naked together
since they're at a hot springs inn!
Right in a bath tub about this big!
Both Darling and Reine packed in tight!
It's the world's greatest packed lunch!
Shido, go with 2.
Roger.
Shin, can I come in?
Oh, yes, go ahead.
Wha?!
Whoa!
What is the meaning of this?!
I can't see Analyst Murasame's na—
No, I can't see our important conquest screen!
Dear god! Bring it back at once!
Our objective is to make
the Spirit fall for him.
I believe it best to avoid doing things
Reine would find unpleasant
after we've sealed her spirit power.
No!
Kannazuki, you're still calm.
Yes.
Because I don't have
much interest in big breasts.
That so?
We're all alone, so you don't mind, right?
N-No...
Those are quite something...
Um, Reine,
how long have you been with Ratatoskr?
It was around five or six years ago?
It was around the same time
Kotori became the commander.
I see.
You know, thank you.
For what?
Well, that means you've been
supporting Kotori all this time.
I haven't done anything that important.
I'm sure she would be a great
commander even without me.
Well, I won't deny that Kotori is talented,
but what did you do before then?
I was your typical student.
My thesis got recognition,
so I was scouted for Ratatoskr.
Was there anyone you fell in love with?
There was one person.
Was that...?
It's not fair to talk about just me.
Would you tell me more about yourself, too?
Huh?
S-Sure.
I've been wanting to hear more
about you for a long time, too.
Do you remember anything that happened
before you were taken in by the Itsuka family?
Honestly, I don't really have
any clear memories.
What I do remember...
is the sensation of being held by warm hands,
and a sense of loss like those hands
were leaving me behind.
I'm sure...
that must have been my mother.
Do you resent your mother for abandoning you?
Huh?
I don't resent her or anything.
I'm sure she had her reasons for it.
I doubt she abandoned me because she wanted to.
Besides, I remember.
I remember how kind
the hands that held me were.
I see...
Huh?
There, there.
Hey, Reine?!
A little of this won't hurt, will it?
Though I may not be able to replace her.
Ellen, sorry for the suddenness,
but I've decided to speed up our plans.
The situation has changed.
Rather, it seems it's about to change.
What do you mean, Ike?
Honestly, I really am fortunate.
Never before have I felt like it was destiny
that the omniscient Beelzebub
was the first Demon King I obtained.
Meaning you've learned
some new fact through Beelzebub?
Precisely.
Apparently we've already suffered
painful defeat once before.
In a future unknown to us.
However, this time we can strike first.
Start preparing the magic reactor.
We'll want absorption charms as well.
Then the Spirit of Origin...?
Come on, Ellen.
Let's change the future as well.
What is it you wanted to show me, Shin?
We're almost there.
I'm sure you'll like it.
We're here.
You can open your eyes now.
This is!
This is the place I wanted to show you, Reine.
It's pretty, right?
Yes, it is pretty.
Very much so.
Episode 9
A "Second" Date
Episode 10: "A Battlefield That Shouldn't Be Possible"
The final battle with Westcott is here.
Who will seize the future? DEM? Or Ratatoskr?
Next time is Episode 10:
"A Battlefield That Shouldn't Be Possible."
All three siblings have gathered.